(Sheldon:)in our living room,
(Sheldon:)and night after night of
uninformative TV documentaries
(Sheldon:)about the Jersey Shore.
(Leonard:)Suffered in silence?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)And I'd thank you to do the same.
Reall-- Silence?!
(sighs): Ah.
(Raj:)Nothing makes beer
taste better than
(Raj:)cool clear Rocky
Mountain spring water.
(Raj:)Where are the Rocky
Mountains, anyway?
(Howard:)Philadelphia.
(Amy:)Really?
(Raj:)I thought they were
out West someplace.
(Howard:)Think about it, Raj.
Where did the movie
Rocky take place?
(Howard:)Philadelphia.
(Raj:)Okay, now I get it.
(Penny:)So this is the plan?
(Penny:)From now on, we're just
gonna hide out in here
(Penny:)to avoid the Shamy?
(Raj:)I'm very comfortable here.
(Raj:)Penny, dear, why don't you shoot
another silver bullet my way?